neurosciencenews.com 2018-10-20

# Neuroscience News Privacy Policy - Neuroscience News

### Privacy Policy  
_Effective July 6, 2010_

 **Our Commitment To Privacy  
**  
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

 **The Information We Collect:**

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the NeuroscienceNews.com website. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are:

Name  
Address  
Email address  
Phone number  
Credit/Debit Card Information

On some pages, you can submit information about other people. For example, if you order a gift online and want it sent directly to the recipient, you will need to submit the recipient’s address. In this circumstance, the types of personal information collected are:

Name  
Address  
Phone Number

 **The Way We Use Information:**

We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.

We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form. We try our best not to disclose anything that could be used to identify individuals.

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

 **Our Commitment To Data Security**

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

 **Our Commitment To Children’s Privacy:**

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.

 **How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information**

You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by logging in to your Neuroscience News account and checking your profile. You can change your information displayed on Neuroscience News by going into your profile and settings areas and following the instructions there. Should you have any further questions, email us, or message us and we will do our best to help you. We will safeguard your information to the best of our capabilities.

You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by making changes in your member profile and settings areas, or sending us a request describing the error and your preferred outcome with the situation.

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections to member account information.

 **How To Contact Us**

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please leave us a comment on a post, page, or forum. You can also email us at [contact @ neurosciencenews.com].

 **Advertising Information**

Only Google and their ad network partners serve ads on our website currently. We do not share your data with anyone and we do our best to protect any data that is left on our website. We do not email users, nor share any data outside of that used by Google and their partners. Below is information regarding Google and their networks, as well as ways to opt-out of sharing data.

Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to this website.

Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and/or other sites on the Internet. Read about [DART here](https://www.google.com/doubleclick/).

Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [advertising opt-out page here](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/ads/).

Alternatively, you can opt out of a third-party vendor’s use of cookies by visiting the [Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page](https://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

A full list of possible vendors on this website is available below and links for more information and to opt-out from certain vendors are available [here](https://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp) and [here](https://support.google.com/dfp_sb/bin/answer.py?hl=en&answer=94149).

Adacado / Healthpricer Interactive  
Adform  
AdMotion  
AdGear (Bloom Digital)  
Aggregate Knowledge  
Adspeed  
ADTECH  
ARC Media  
Bluestreak  
Calibex (NextTag)  
Chemistry.com  
Cossette  
DoubleClick  
(DFP Small Business not supported,  
DFP Enterprise certified is individually)  
e-planning  
eBay  
Emediate  
eyeReturn  
Flashtalking  
Flite  
Facilitate Digital  
Hamilton Beach  
Match.com  
MediaMind  
Mediaplex  
Newtention  
OpenX  
Optimum Response  
Sapient/BridgeTrack  
SiteScout  
Tassimo  
uSwitch  
TruEffect  
Wall Street on Demand/Adhesion  
Zedo  
Adform  
AdKeeper  
AdMotion  
ARC Media  
Bluestreak  
Brightroll  
Buzzlogic  
Cossette  
DoubleClick  
eyeReturn  
Flashtalking  
Interpolls  
Kwanzoo  
Linkstorm  
MediaMind  
Mediaplex  
Pointroll  
Oggifinogi  
Pictela  
Pointroll  
Poprule  
Qoof  
SocialMedia  
Spongecell  
Teracent  
Tumri  
Unicast  
United Virtualities  
Expandable Ads:  
DoubleClick  
EyeWonder  
Flashtalking  
Interpolls  
Linkstorm  
MediaMind  
Mediaplex  
Pointroll  
comScore/ScorecardResearch*  
Constant Contact*  
GfK Daphne*  
Global Market Insite*  
MeMo2*  
MetrixLab*  
Nielsen/IAG (RewardTV)*  
Nielsen/NetEffect (Homescan)*  
Nurago*  
TNS Global/Compete Inc.*  
comScore/VoiceFive*  
Dimestore*  
Dynamic Logic/Safecount*  
Symphony Advanced Media (formerly Factor TG)*  
InsightExpress*  
MetrixLab*  
OTX Research/Safecount*  
TNS Global/Compete Inc.*  
Vizu*  
comScore/VoiceFive*  
Dimestore* Dynamic Logic/Safecount*  
Symphony Advanced Media (formerly Factor TG)*  
InsightExpress*  
MetrixLab*  
OTX Research/Safecount*  
TNS Global/Compete Inc.*  
Vizu* Dimestore*  
Dynamic Logic/Safecount (Adometer)*  
OTX Research/Safecount (Adometer)*  
Vizu*  
24/7 Real Media/Open AdStream (OAS)*  
Adclear  
Adroit Interactive  
Ally.com*  
Channel Intelligence*  
Constant Contact*  
Coremetrics*  
LiveRail  
Sophus3*  
Target.com* VideoHub  
Coremetrics*  
Encore Metrics*  
Explido WebMarketing/ActionAllocator*  
Dynamo (Innovid)*  
MetrixLab*  
Nielsen/NetRatings (NetView)*  
Nurago* VideoHub  
comScore/ScorecardResearch*  
Quantcast*  
TNS Global/Compete Inc.*  
Adometry*  
DoubleVerify* DoubleVerify*  
Evidon (formerly Better Advertising)* TRUSTe*

*All of the vendors listed have links to their sites [here](https://support.google.com/dfp_sb/bin/answer.py?hl=en&answer=94149) and can be used to opt-out of information sharing, or to learn more about the networks. Any additional vendors that are allowed to serve ads should be listed at that page.

If you have any questions about opting out of ads, or your information and privacy, please contact us at contact @ neurosciencenews.com.
